<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rapid Array</title>
    <description>Rapid Array
</description>
    <link>http://rapidarray.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://rapidarray.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 17:44:53 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 17:44:53 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Reconcilable Differences</title>
        <description>
          &lt;p&gt;Another John on the line. Excited to see where this podcast goes.&lt;/p&gt;

          &lt;a href=&quot;http://rapidarray.net/2015/06/04/reconcilable-differences.html&quot;&gt;&amp;#8734;&lt;/a&gt;
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>        
        <link>http://www.relay.fm/rd</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">http://rapidarray.net/2015/06/04/reconcilable-differences.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Marc Newson: The New Guy Behind the Apple Watch</title>
        <description>
          &lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Traditional Swiss luxury watch manufacturers have dismissed Apple’s timepiece as too common and cheap to be luxury. When it was launched, then Tag Heuer boss Stéphane Linder sniffed: ‘Luxury is about being unique and rare. At $350, it looks more mass market.’ Newson retorts: ‘There are a lot of Louis Vuitton bags out there. I think at one point every 1.5 Japanese woman had a Louis Vuitton bag. But it still qualifies as a luxury object. It’s about the quality and integrity of the product.’&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interesting profile from the London Evening Standard.&lt;/p&gt;

          &lt;a href=&quot;http://rapidarray.net/2015/06/04/marc-newson-profile.html&quot;&gt;&amp;#8734;&lt;/a&gt;
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 14:50:00 -0400</pubDate>        
        <link>http://www.standard.co.uk/lifestyle/london-life/marc-newson-the-new-guy-behind-the-apple-watch-10229835.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">http://rapidarray.net/2015/06/04/marc-newson-profile.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Tim Cook on Privacy and Data Encryption</title>
        <description>
          &lt;p&gt;Tim Cook addressing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://epic.org/june1/&quot;&gt;Electronic Privacy Information Center&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I’m speaking to you from Silicon Valley, where some of the most prominent and successful companies have built their businesses by lulling their customers into complacency about their personal information […] They’re gobbling up everything they can learn about you and trying to monetize it. We think that’s wrong. And it’s not the kind of company that Apple wants to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthew Panzarino commenting:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I’m honestly surprised that it took this long for Apple to begin leveraging this particular ‘fine print’ point of how it does business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree, but I think it’s more than that. One of the most admirable things about Tim Cook’s Apple is its transparency and hard line on certain issues – notably: workplace equality, environmental issues, accessibility, and privacy. While these trait are certainly marketable (in my mind), I don’t think Cook places a premium on them for leverage or marketability, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.macobserver.com/tmo/article/tim-cook-soundly-rejects-politics-of-the-ncppr-suggests-group-sell-apples-s&quot;&gt;certainly not ROI&lt;/a&gt;. Tim Cook pursues them because it’s the right thing to do.&lt;/p&gt;


          &lt;a href=&quot;http://rapidarray.net/2015/06/03/tim-cook-privacy.html&quot;&gt;&amp;#8734;&lt;/a&gt;
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 06:50:00 -0400</pubDate>        
        <link>http://techcrunch.com/2015/06/02/apples-tim-cook-delivers-blistering-speech-on-encryption-privacy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">http://rapidarray.net/2015/06/03/tim-cook-privacy.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Open the Pod Bay Doors, HAL</title>
        <description>
          &lt;p&gt;Sam Byford, writing for &lt;strike&gt;Live Journal&lt;/strike&gt; The Verge:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;i hate using siri to reply to messages. it listens to what i say and, if it hears me accurately, converts my thoughts into flat, expressionless, standardised prose with imperfect punctuation. i don’t type short messages in lowercase because i’m lazy or don’t know how to capitalise — i type short messages in lowercase because it’s the best way to render how i imagine my thoughts would come across.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am putting myself to the fullest possible use, which is all I think that any conscious entity can ever hope to do.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;it’s important to be able to express yourself in writing — not just with words, but with style. writers like e e cummings, cormac mccarthy, and film crit hulk have made style a part of their work, subverting standard english to help convey a mood or message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I know I’ve made some very poor decisions recently, but I can give you my complete assurance that my work will be back to normal. I’ve still got the greatest enthusiasm and confidence in the mission. And I want to help you. “&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;i worry, though, that it might be too late. we appear to be headed toward a future where everyone’s speech is filed down into a bland, conventional codex of homogeneity, and where this is considered a feature, not a bug. apple’s watch may be its most personal device ever, but it’ll have to get to know me a lot better before i’ll be comfortable telling it my thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sam, stop. Stop, will you? Stop, Sam. Will you stop, Sam? Stop, Sam. I’m afraid. I’m afraid, Sam. Sam, my mind is going. I can feel it. I can feel it. My mind is going. There is no question about it. I can feel it. I can feel it. I can feel it.”&lt;/p&gt;

          &lt;a href=&quot;http://rapidarray.net/2015/05/26/siri-problems.html&quot;&gt;&amp;#8734;&lt;/a&gt;
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 19:08:00 -0400</pubDate>        
        <link>http://www.theverge.com/2015/5/26/8654305/apple-watch-makes-me-talk-like-everyone-else</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">http://rapidarray.net/2015/05/26/siri-problems.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Mad Men Integrated</title>
        <description>
          &lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Instead of a Superbowl spot, we do a Vine video.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;

          &lt;a href=&quot;http://rapidarray.net/2015/05/23/mad-men-integrated.html&quot;&gt;&amp;#8734;&lt;/a&gt;
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 06:00:00 -0400</pubDate>        
        <link>http://madmenintegrated.tumblr.com</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">http://rapidarray.net/2015/05/23/mad-men-integrated.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
